

PROFILE

A 20-year-old self-motivated and passionate student from Gorkha of Western Nepal. I am a young, energetic and enthusiastic person who can face any challenges that appear on my way to get success in the field of my interest. I like seeing the practicality of situations and act accordingly.

AWARDS

National Merit Scholarship Award SII Scholarship Award

CONTACT

PHONE: +91-7894129176

CURRENT LOCATION:

Bhubaneswar, Odisha, India

EMAIL:

binayaktv@gmail.com

LINKEDIN PROFILE:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/binayakkoirala-4200b1193/

GIT HUB LINK:

https://github.com/BinayakKoirala

SOCIAL MEDIA:

https://www.instagram.com/ bineyyy

https://twitter.com/sarcastovert

HOBBIES

Playing Cricket Gaming Travelling

BINAYAK KOIRALA

EDUCATION

KALINGA INSTITUTE OF INDUSTRIAL TECHNOLOGY (Bachelor in Computer Science and Engineering)

December, 2020 — Present (9.60/10 CGPA), 5th Semester

National School of Sciences(High-School)

July,2017—August,2019

(3.73/4.0 CGPA). National Merit Scholarship holder.

Siddhartha Vanasthali Institute(School)

May,2015—June,2017 (3.8/4.0 CGPA)

WORK EXPERIENCE

TRADER AT NEPSE

October 2020 — December 2021 Group of 4 people, trading and investing in different companies.

Gift card Virtual Nepal - (Startup)

September, 2019—June, 2021 Small business of selling gaming products.

Job-oriented Digital Marketing

August,2019— December,2019 Handling the social media accounts of the company.

SKILLS ON COMPUTER

- -MS EXCEL as Data Analysis
- -MS OFFICE
- -Python programming (Intermediate)
- -Some Minor projects on Python
- -Python framework Django and Flask (Beginner)
- -Python as an Exploratory Data Analysis (Beginner)
- -Data structures and algorithm

KEY SKILLS

Public Speaking: Debates, poems, essay

Proficient in three languages: English, Nepali, Hindi **Sports involvement:** Cricket, Football, Table-tennis

Campaign planning